[Music]
we live in an uncertain and
unpredictable World it has become
extremely critical to plan today to
secure our tomorrow presenting ICICI Pro
guaranteed income for tomorrow
gift a savings plus insurance plan that
allows you to save systematically and
grow your money with 100 guaranteed
tax-free returns while also giving you a
life cover to ensure your loved ones are
financially secure even in your absence
whether you are a millennial looking to
start your investment Journey a regular
investor looking for fixed tax-free
returns
A working woman looking to create a
second income stream
a parent saving for your child's
education a businessman securing your
retirement or an achiever who wants to
fulfill his goal of buying a house car
or going on that dream vacation a
guaranteed Savings Plan like gift forms
an integral part of your financial
portfolio the ICICI approved gift plan
comes with three options income early
income and lump sum in this video we
will take a look at the gift early
income option here you can set aside and
invest a fixed amount from your income
for a specified time period and get a
guaranteed flow of income while you are
still contributing from the second year
itself let's understand this better with
an example
is a 25 year old professional looking to
invest systematically and also get her
money back in the form of returns while
she is contributing
she decides to purchase a gift early
income plan online
and invest rupees 10 000 per month for
10 years she selects the annual payout
mode she receives an income of rupees
2500 per month from the second year
itself called early guaranteed income
till the 11th year and a larger
guaranteed income of rupees 1.54 lakh
per year from the 11th year till the
20th year considering both the early
income and regular income she will get a
total of rupees 18.37 lakh by investing
just rupees 10 000 per month for 10
years and the best part this return is
fixed irrespective of declining interest
rates and unpredictable Market scenarios
by investing in the gift plan Aditi will
get the dual benefit of tax savings on
premiums paid and tax free returns
moreover she can get income when she
wants with a unique save feature she can
also Avail a loan against a policy in
case of any financial needs along with
guaranteed income this plan also gives
Aditi a life cover to secure the
well-being of her loved ones in case of
any unfortunate event buying this plan
online is safe secure and convenient
plus you also get to enjoy 3.5 percent
additional maturity benefit so what are
you waiting for visit
iciciprolife.com to create a plan for
yourself today you can also call us at
[Music]
1-800-209-9007 and our insurance experts
will be glad to assist you investment
plans starting at just rupees 2500 per
month